Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/harrmahar (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Penetration Testing
Information Security
Kali Linux

Certifications

Certified Appsec Practicioner (CAP)
Certified Red Team Analyst (CRTA)
Certified Ethical Hacker (CEH)
CompTIA PenTest+
Offensive Security Certified
Professional (OSCP)

Publications

Pemodelan Serangan Advanced Persistent Threat dengan Diamond Model of Intrusion Analysis dan Kill Chain

Satrya Mahardhika

OSCP | CRTA | CEH | Pentest+| Penetration Tester at BSSN | Ethical Hacking Instructor

West Java, Indonesia

Summary

Experienced Cyber Security Analyst with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Information Security, Computer Security, Testing, Penetration Testing, and Kali Linux. Strong information technology professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Information Technology from Sekolah Tinggi Sandi Negara.

Experience

Badan Siber dan Sandi Negara 5 years 5 months

Penetration Tester August 2021 - Present (3 years 7 months) Jakarta, Indonesia

Cyber Security Analyst October 2019 - August 2021 (1 year 11 months) Jakarta

Education

Sekolah Tinggi Sandi Negara Bachelor's degree, Information Technology · (2015 - 2019)